I thought I was good at going it alone
Would you prefer to go together?
Place
your finger here
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Legitimate Girlfriend"
I'm sorry for lying to you for so long!
I'm a rental girlfriend.
"Mizuhara Chizuru" is my pseudonym.
My real name is Ichinose Chizuru.
I apologize for all the concern
I've caused you over all this.
At first, I only saw this as work.
I was a "girlfriend,"
and Kazuya-san was my client.
But as I got to know
Kazuya-san's strength of
character and his kind personality,
I stopped thinking of him as
just a client at some point.
I'm sorry. I was too taken aback to
respond to your questions right away.
I'm sure you'll still have your doubts,
but as you've seen,
nothing's going to change.
I'm legitimately Kazuya-san's
girlfriend now.
Wha...
Right?
O-Oh, yeah!
That's right! Yeah, yeah!
W-We'll continue to live up
to Sayuri-san's wishes...
W-Wai—
Wait a damn second!
I-I didn't get a good view.
Did you really kiss?
She might've just faked it and kissed
him on the cheek or something.
I wouldn't put it past
a rental girlfriend.
They might still be trying to
worm their way out of this.
Wh-What are you saying now, Mami-chan?!
Right, Kibe-chan? You couldn't
see it either, could you?
Huh? I mean, I guess...
Wha...
How about now?
Yikes.
I saw it this time.
Please, no more!
Think about the other guests!
I'm truly sorry about the fuss.
We'll take this elsewhere right away.
Kazuya, Chizuru-san.
Get changed and come to my room.
After that, we explained everything.
Not with the usual lies and things
we made up on the spot,
but how we met, how we went to the same
college and were next-door neighbors,
how she was an actress...
How we ended up making a movie,
and what happened in
Sayuri-san's last moments.
Mizuhara handled most of the talking,
with Gran asking questions here and there.
Mizuhara would then reply to them,
getting as close to the truth as possible.
All I could do was sit there
and nod along every so often.
Rental Girlfriend
In the next two hours, we ended up
coming clean about almost all of it.
All but the lie that we'd been dating
since a week before Sayuri-san passed.
Okay, it all adds up now. I'm satisfied.
I said it was for Sayuri-san, but I
jumped to conclusions and condemned you.
Pardon this old coot for her
momentary lapse in judgment.
I apologize for doubting you.
I hope you can forgive me, Chizuru-san.
Please, it's fine.
Also...
Ow!
You! You caused this mess by
not giving Mami-dono the news!
Learn your lesson!!
Well, it's time for dinner.
Let's head
to the lobby
I'll help explain this to everyone else.
We appreciate it.
They probably can't eat
anything as things stand.
We're truly sorry for worrying you.
Don't mention it.
Anyway, we're keeping them waiting.
Right.
I got the details.
I'll tell you when we're inside.
Got it.
Kazuya, did you actually dry your hair?
Relax, okay?
And that's the long and short of it.
And that's how
they got together
Okay, it all makes sense.
You could've told us about
your rental girlfriend job, though.
That wouldn't change
our relationship
I-I'm sorry. I just
couldn't bring myself to.
Where's Kibe?
On a walk, he said.
You two knew about it, right?
And it doesn't affect your friendship?
Huh? R-Right!
Of course!
Anyway, we're back to square one.
The workings of society can cause
friction in the closest relationships.
In order to protect the other clients,
Chizuru-san couldn't bring it up,
and I fully understand that.
Considering
social norms
As long as their feelings are real,
nothing else really matters.
We can work on having better
communication in the future.
For now, let us have dinner.
Excuse me. I have to use the restroom.
Of course. Run along.
Let's go grab our food.
Hey, one sec!
Kuri?
What the heck's going on?
Are you two dating for real?!
I thought Chizuru-san was just
pretending as part of her job!
Isn't that what you
told me yesterday?!
But now it looks like...
That's how it looks
to you, too, huh?
Of course not. Me and Mizuhara?
Just think
about it
I dunno
anymore,
man!
Then what is the deal?!
Explain it like I'm five!!
Us being together for real is a lie.
Mizuhara just played along with it.
Played along? She went way beyond that!
I mean, that was...
a kiss! She kissed you!
Do you really
get it?
I-I get it, okay?
I had no idea
that was coming!
What did Chizuru-san say?
We haven't had the chance to talk.
You panicking
chicken!!
Wha? Are you kidding me,
you absolute moron?!
Anyway, I just gotta play it cool, right?
Like always
I'm not touching this
with a ten-foot pole.
Sounds right. Thanks.
Listen, Kazuya. She's probably broken
the ToS a buncha times to help you!
This trip, that theme park outing...
I get how nice Chizuru-san is!
But Kazuya... I'm gonna say it again!
That was a kiss! She kissed you, dude!
Are you
unwell?
What are you two doing?
Oh... I dropped some nuts on the floor.
L-Let's go, Nagomi-san.
Man, Kibe sure is
taking his time
Gah! What the hell?!
scratch scratch
Look at
that guy, Dad
It's always
summertime here
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Hey!
What are you playing at?
Seriously, what are you thinking?!
R-Ruka-chan.
Do you realize what you did?!
Have you forgotten that
you're a rental girlfriend?!
C-Calm down, will you?
How could I? You cucked me
in front of my own eyes!
Cucked?! I wouldn't call it that...
Well, I would! What if Kazuya-kun
really falls for you now?
It had to be done for work?
You really think that's gonna fly?!
Go out with her.
Didn't you encourage Kazuya-kun back then?
Didn't you say you were
rooting for the two of us?!
I remember what you said
to me that New Year's.
You said you don't really want
to be with Kazuya-kun!
Do you seriously believe you're
helping his grandma like this?!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Wh-What's with the sudden
pain in your eyes?
I'm not falling for your
emotional manipulation.
I've had enough of your nonsense!
M-Mami-san...
You still call this work?
Are you out of your mind?!
And this rental girlfriend crap can't
even be called work in the first place!
If this is a joke, it's not at all funny!
Stop it right this instant!
H-Hey, take it easy!
Well, you didn't hold up your end of
the deal. You went and ratted us out.
What?! You can't seriously be
trying to shift the blame here!
This basically proves that you were
willfully seducing him all this time!
I can't stand the way
you look down on people!
You whisper your sweet nothings
and wash your hands of the guilt!
You just kissed your own client, you know!
How are you any different
from a shady prostitute?!
You make me sick!
Forget it! I'm calling your agency!
Hey, hold up.
What?! Why are you stopping me?!
I mean, I think you're going too far.
I think there's something
wrong with you, too.
You can't be serious!
You think you can talk?
S-Slow down, you two!
How about you stop lying to yourself?
Don't you realize how weird it is that
you're this obsessed with Kazuya-san?
D-Don't go there, Chizuru-san!
I really am sorry about today.
I know it's unacceptable.
I'll admit that this goes
beyond the scope of work.
All I can do is ask that you keep
it a secret from my agency.
If you think I'm being defiant, so be it.
And if you want further apologies,
I'll get down on my knees right here.
But... But still...
I think it can wait until after you've
come to terms with your own feelings.
Excuse me.
What? Wait up, Chizuru-san!
Fuck!
Chizuru-san said she was turning in early.
She seemed in rather low spirits.
After all that happened, I can see why.
Let's give her some space for now.
I-I'm hitting the restroom.
Nobody's listening
What is even
happening?
God damn!
My brain can't keep up!
O God!!
He's the kind of guy
who wracks his brain on the can
They found out about the
rental girlfriend thing,
and when I said we really were
together, Mami-chan told us to kiss?
And then, and then...
Whoa,
that's scary
That was a kiss! She kissed you, dude!
I was trying not to think about it,
but that's all I can think about now!
It's his fault for reminding me
Mizuhara and I just kissed!
Well, yeah, we've broken
the rules several times!
Even if you just look at this trip,
it's a parade of violations!
Swimsuit and whatnot
But I still feel like we've
clearly crossed a line now!
Are you kidding me?!
Mizuhara and I kissed!
We kissed!
There was no doubt about it.
That was paradise!
The warmth like the gentle
embrace of sunlight...
The scent of a flower
field in full bloom...
It was otherworldly.
It was a feeling, a moment in time,
that I couldn't escape!
I burn up every time I recall it!
I thought the softest part
of a girl's body was the tiddy!
Cool down, you moron!
Don't get carried away
by the fake summer here!
But seriously, how does she feel
about it? We kissed, you know!
I know we had our backs against the wall,
but can you really
kiss a guy you don't like?!
What could this mean?!
Mizuhara!!
Welp, that hit him hard
Gulp
Gah!
I came after her,
but what am I trying to do here?
I'm alone with Mizuhara
after that happened?
That,
which
happened
What do I wanna ask her?
Straight
as an arrow
"What did you mean by that?"
"What did you kiss me for?"
No way! It's too risky!
Here stands a delusional moron who's
thinking with his dick right now!
Wow, you're in heat.
Whoa
What have
we here?
Wait, she might already have
the ick because I came after her!
My world
is pink
I can't. My mind won't get
out of horny mode after that kiss.
I am hopelessly conscious of
every nook and cranny of Mizuhara!
Can you blame me?
No matter the reason,
she and I just kissed four hours ago!
With this angel CG-superimposed
onto this world! With Mizuhara!
Sexy
Her hair's so pretty!
Her wrists are so pretty!
Sexy
Help! Every cell of her
looks pretty to me right now!
Pretty
Sexy
It's okay,
right, Kuri?!
That was a kiss!
She kissed you, dude!
But... I'm allowed to ask, right?
S-Say, Mizuhara...
It's not like that was
the first time, right?
She means that one time?
That counted?
That was the second time.
We'd already broken the rules.
I had no other choice in that moment.
It's honestly pathetic that
we're still making excuses.
But I agree that ending it by saying
we broke up would be best.
Even if not right away,
it'd make sense if we told them
this whole mess made us drift apart.
So she did it to maintain the status quo?
Mostly, I couldn't just watch it play out.
Mami-san wasn't exactly wrong
with what she said.
I understand that what I'm doing is wrong.
I'm not entirely blameless.
If anything, you were telling me to come
clean to my grandma until the very end.
Sorry, that's my issue to deal with.
Anyway, I couldn't stand the idea
of it all being your fault alone.
Better be ready to see this through.
I won't let you play the hero
and end this all by yourself.
I've got
somewhere to be
Mizuhara...
So you were sticking up for me.
She was like,
no big deal!
But really? She was totally
casual about the kiss!
It was
business
like usual
So she'll admit that it went
beyond work, but that's really it?
Ugh, I feel like I said a lotta
things I shouldn't have.
Self-hatred
Death by Shame
Just recalling them makes me wanna die!
But really?
I mean, yeah, that wasn't our first time.
And if she hadn't done that, Gran and
Kibe would've lost all hope in me by now.
Kuri, I don't know anymore.
We're talking about Mizuhara Chizuru here.
The queen of the dating jungle.
Chizuru-san said that?
Yes, she texted me just now.
She wants the three of us
to room together again.
I see. Well, a lot happened today,
so you would all need a distraction.
So, where is Mizuhara?
Where'd she go?
Beats me.
I haven't heard
Another walk?
Well, it was an eventful day,
so she must have a lot on her mind.
Still, what a crazy trip.
I caused lots of trouble
for Mizuhara again.
What's the meaning of this?!
That was the only way
I could sort that mess out!
Yeah, but you crossed the line there!
Now the rental girlfriend lie is done for,
but now the "we're not lying
about dating" lie remains.
Ugh! You two are getting a talking-to
once Chizuru-san's back!
All night!
And where'd she go, anyway?
In the end, I still don't know
how Mizuhara feels about all this.
Is it so wrong to assign any kind
of significance to the kiss?
clench...
Mizuhara...
We're total strangers, aren't we?
It doesn't matter how much
you care for your partner!
I won't rent Mizuhara Chizuru out anymore.
Mizuhara!
I'll do it!
Let's make a movie together!
I swear I'll see it through!
Please take one!
You know what my ideal girlfriend's like?
I swear I'll protect you from the blame!
Mizuhara's not that kind of person.
That's the Mizuhara Chizuru
I've come to love!
Do you know when true love begins?
It's when you're having the time
of your life talking about them.
I told you, that's not what this is.
I can't do it. He's my client.
I can't fall in love with him.
After all, there's no way to
get your true self on rental.
What are you laughing at, Grandma?
I can't believe you kissed another
girl in front of your girlfriend!
Right... I really kissed Mizuhara.
Are you listening to me?!
Huh? You said we kissed?
That's not what I'm not talking about!
And heck, you've kissed me too, remember?
Uh...
Fine! I'm gonna overwrite it!
Whoa, whoa! Stop right there!
Next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Long Time No...
...Girlfriend."
It's been a while! Let's get cozy!
"Long Time No Girlfriend"
T-Timeout!